Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sanah-qasemb57933b0 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Medicine Hospitals

Healthcare

Sanah Qasem

NHS Doctor, Aesthetic Dr, Clinical Director & Principal Trainer at Derma Medical.

London, England Metropolitan Area

Summary

Dr Sanah Qasem is a full-time NHS Doctor and Aesthetic injector performing the latest basic and advanced treatments with neurotoxins (Botox), Dermal fillers, Silhouette one stitch and PDO thread face lifts, skin rejuvenation/peels and aquaplasty/intralipotherapy body sculpting treatments.

She divides her aesthetic work between her busy Derma Medical Clinics

in London Harley Street, and is the Clinical and Educational Director at the Derma Medical Training Academies in London, Manchester, Sweden, Dubai and Australia where she travels regularly.

Dr Qasem previously worked for the UK's leading Aesthetic company -Transform Cosmetic Surgery Group in London and is a member of the Medical Education Committee for the world leading Aesthetic manufacturing company - Teoxane. In addition to that, she is a Key opinion Leader for the Medical Aesthetic Company Intraline.

Dr Qasem graduated from medical school with distinctions and has been awarded prizes for academic and clinical excellence, as well as receiving merits for Teaching and Leadership from South Thames Foundation school. Alongside this, she has been chosen twice as the Teaching lead for trainee doctors across trusts in South East England. It is her experience in clinical education with her knowledge and passion for Aesthetic medicine that has led her to become the principal Trainer at Derma Medical Training Academy, where she teaches over 25 different aesthetic treatments to medical professionals at the Royal College of General Practitioners in London, Manchester, Sweden, Australia and Dubai.

Experience

Derma Medical
Owner and Advanced Injector

April 2014 - Present (6 years 5 months)

Harley Street London, United Kingdom

Owner and Advanced Injector at Derma Medical Clinics

Transform Cosmetic Surgery Group Aesthetic Doctor 2015 - Present (5 years) London, Maidstone, United Kingdom

DermaMedical

Clinical and Educational Director for Dermal Medical London, Manchester, Sweden, Dubai, Australia 2015 - Present (5 years)

London, United Kingdom

Clinical Director - Leading Aesthetic training and Masterclasses

Educational Director -developing the curriculum and techniques for the latest aesthetic procedures.

Principal Trainer - Teaching Basic and Advanced Botulinum toxin & dermal filler treatments.

NHS England Doctor August 2014 - Present (6 years 1 month) London, United Kingdom

Intraline®
Medical Advisory Board Member
September 2015 - Present (5 years)

Teoxane Laboratories
Medical Education Steering Committee Member
November 2016 - Present (3 years 10 months)
London, United Kingdom

A New You (Brighton) Ltd Aesthetic Doctor 2014 - January 2017 (3 years) Brighton, United Kingdom

Aesthetic injector of Basic and Advanced Botox and Dermal filler treatments, one stitch silhouette thread lifts, body sculpting, skin care and peels.

Education

Brighton and Sussex Medical School
Bachelor of Medicine, Bachelor of Surgery (MBBS), Medicine